You know where the islands of the
plastics are floating? They have a certain,
set pattern, yeah? And Jallal just showed that,
when he puts CH3 or Deuterium, the
plastic has the way to go towards it. So,
that rang a bell in my head when you use
Deuterium, I said then there must be
something going on deeper in the crust
of the Earth, because Deuterium has
decayed. So, I said maybe that might be
related to the magma or volcanic high
movement.
I said, maybe it will even match, where
Mr. Keshe was explaining about the
earthquakes and the snapping of the
plates. So, now we try to bring it into a
map, and I said if anyone can find
anything what is shown above these
fields - that might explain why the
plastics are held in place, or they're
moving together - from one part to the
other - in more dense concentration. I said,
we were nearly about preparing
everything to come off for Thursday, I
said, but I said it might be good to
invite Mr. Keshe, maybe we'll receive some
more answers. So, they all have agreed to
invite you here. So, if you can share it
again. There it is. Can you see it Mr.
Keshe?
He even has moving, or rotating, life
rotating, that the plastic - how it travels
from one point to another. These are the
concentration points. Annie can you show
the other one, please? I might get broken
off because we have a very bad internet
today in China. All the VPNs are
shutting down very rapidly, because
there's some problems. (CK) I'm getting cut off, because I'm getting... You found it Vernie? (inaudible). Am I correct with the assumption that
something decay is going on deeper in, to
attract these huge islands or masses of
plastic to stay in position and move
together? (MK) It's internal field forces which
matches. (CK) Yeah, but if it's Deuterium,
plastic is not Deuterium. (MK) This is not a
Deuterium, this is a C-H bond.
Even Deuterium is a H3 plasma condition.
(CK) So, what is going on...
(MK) It's a... What happened, you have a deuterium,
when you call it the H2. But it doesn't neccessarily
behave as H2, it behaves as H3.
All the plastics have some sort of a CH3
bond, or CH bond. This is where most of
protein is gathering, most probably. And
if you look at it, if you look at the map.
If he can put what was up before? If you
can't put it up? Can somebody? Can we have
the picture, which was there before - the
two circles? You see. Can you open it up?
If you can open that up. These are, most of
these, what we know...
Hello, can you hear me? (CK) Yes, yes.
(MK) I had a problem here with my system.
(CK) But if you look from the right side, go to the right circle, it's like
in one line, around the planet. (MK) Yeah, but
these are. Just one second, I have to give
an answer. You see, when you... Where is it?
Where have I lost the Zoom? Hello? (CK) We are still there, Mr Keshe. (MK) I don't have a...
(CK) Can you see the screen? (J) I think he want to
annotate. (MK) No, there's something wrong with
the picture. Can you move it up? Can we see
the both circles, please? (VG) This one is, this
one is the first side, showing the
Pacific Ocean. The other one is showing
the Atlantic Ocean. (MK) Yeah, we want to see the
Atlantic ocean, please. If you...
Okay. If you look at these two, the all
four of them, these are what we call the
protein lines. These are where
most of.... If you bring all the pictures
down together. These are where most of the
protein lines are produced,
where we see majority of the fishes. And what....
You see, where you see in the West Africa,
that area, and where you see the North
China Sea, and the same in the south side.
Can you expand this picture? Okay, just
wait. If you look at all these pictures,
these are what we call a protein line,
which is where we see most of the fishes,
and this is where the carbon-hydrogen
bond stays. When you look at something a
lot of people don't know is... If you look
at, if you look at... There is something
wrong with my phone. If you look at the
African side, for example, just where you
see in the West Africa - north of what you
call it, the West of north of South
Africa. And then you go across to what we
call Amazon. This is where all the Sahara
dust comes. And if there wasn't a Sahara
dust coming annually, right across
Atlantic into Amazon, Amazon would have
been dead. So, what you see, we see what is
known as a protein line. We see the same
thing in North Atlantic and
on the Pacific
side. Where you see on the Pacific with
the red lines, when you look at it, in
what you call
California side, to the other side - you see a lot of these. These are where
South China Sea comes in and brings a
lot of life into the ocean. So, there's a
CH bond, which is a protein bond and they
get attracted to it. And they are part
of the way you do it in your CO2 box,
literally. They are connected.
We looked at this some times ago. This is
what, if you see it is in line and it
goes across South America, Brazil into,
what we call, jungles of
Brazil and it goes across because it's
very thin. All these and the North, is the
same, comes from North China Sea.
This we know and is a characteristics
of the protein absorption. Yes we can see
it, because... It's very eas.y If you look at
the West Africa - the one in the middle. I
cannot, I cannot. There are two-three
reasons what they get, they gather here. If
you look at the West Africa, it comes
down through South Atlantic and it
covers the Amazons, and then it goes
across. This is a protein lin,e this is
where we see most of the fishes. The same when you
look, is a what you call, Pacific, North
Atlantic. It's the same. These are the
feeding lines. If you look at the North
Atlantic and you see the other end of it
is where you get a lot...
We understand partially what this is, but
de-concentration of it. So, is
connected with the central, magnetic,
gravitational fields and... What... If they
were collected in one group, one place, in
one ocean, you would have said is that
place. But it's like a crust and these
plastics we don't see them to
disintegrate. They stay in the salt water
the way they are. And there are some reports
that are very fatty, that they are not
normal. And partially why we think the
animals, a lot of fishes are eating
plastic. Because these plastics through their...
They are in the salt water, so they
taste, they behave like protein. We know
animals - if they eat something wrong, they
spit it out, all the fishes do. But they
swallow it, because is tented
with a protein. We looked at a lot of
this, how the animals... Somebody's
microphone is open. And this is, this, we... There is a behavior to this, is...
First of all it has a connection, CH
bonds with a protein, and it's on a feed
line - we see there are protein ocean
line.
The North American, North Atlantic you
have the same. The Pacific you have the
same. And it is very, very easy. Especially
if you look at South America and it
goes right across the other position, and
if you aligned it, you will see lies
within the structure. These are places
where most of the fish, heavy fishes are
found too. Not the fish as, what we call
the omibs - the origin of life. We
seen it in Australia and the... what they call it,
the South Africa. These are heavy ocean
lines. Now we understand this is
partially the reason. And if you go back
to the teachings, many times I explained.
That's... if you.... I don't have my pen with me,
it's on my desk. If you look for example, the
red sand from Africa, Central Africa
comes over
it covers usually Gambia. Comes to
Sierra Leon and it comes down. If you stay
on the street you go read. It's happened
to me many times. And then it goes over
the Atlantic, and it goes all the way to
what we will call the... all the
jungles, which we see. And they say most
of the oxygen of the world is produced
in these jungles, which is all rubbish -
now we know. And then the rest of it
carries on across, because that part of
South America is very thin. And
then it goes into, what we call, Atlantic
till about Indian Ocean on the other side - if
you look at it that away. And this line
we know, we can't follow it. What you call
the jungles of Brazil, or southern
America, receives estimated, in the region
of 140 million tons of sand from
Central Africa every year. And in that
process the rest of it lies exactly as
we see across continents and it
goes across the continents through to the
other side. And we have the same kind of
process coming through, what we call,
Australia to southern African continent. The
Sahara is, they, if you think. So much,
there are 250 million tons of sand comes off
the Central Africa, all the way across to
Atlantic; over what you call all
the jungles of Amazon and everything going
through to the other side across. Where
does all this sand comes from?
And it happens every year. We have
descenting North China Sea, as you see, in the
North North Pacific, which goes to America.
There are some of these sandstorms
are visible, some of them gets watched
through the operation of the, what we
call, the icebergs. When in the snow time it
comes from Canada, or it comes from
North China. They create this line, we
know these lines very clearly. And if you
look and consider how many millions of
tons of sand, for centuries is going
across, or in the north part. Where does
the sand come from? So, the Earth attracts
these sand particles from the
atmosphere. As much as it releases every
year, we don't see a dip in the desert. We
don't see them running out of sand. The
way the atmosphere produces a protein;
from atmosphere into the sea, and then
ends of it down rains on the fish - the same
thing happens with the desert. And in
that process, it creates a gravitational-
magnetic field of the sand. And then the
gold and that kind of things, all can
come through this. So, the plastics now
have become those sands coming from the
sky. Because of the gravitational
magnetic field of the below, they get
attracted to the same positions. They get
pulled to it - it is the magnetic field
created by it, by the proteins. We don't
see them anywhere else, we see the
majority on the protein line. And if
you look in West Africa, you have the
most richest regions of the fish, because
they go there to eat. All the big fishes
go to have their aminos
from the...The sand from Sahara has a lot
of iron. Mixture with a protein creates
life - the first phase of life with the sugar
and salt in the water; and the
beginning of the planktons.
And then the planktons are purely amino
acid mixture with iron from the Sahara.
Som we understand this and it's just
attached to it, because these plastics
are originally made from the protein-
based petroleum, or gases, which is the
same base so they get attracted to it. We
have made material, which the magnetic
fields of the planet matches to. Now we
understand. It is very easy to get rid of
these plastics in the oceans through the
Keshe Foundation technology. It is rather
easy, so it's part of the program we have
in China, is this. But it cannot be done.
There is something, which I was
explaining to some powerful
diplomats today and yesterday. That
is we have the solution, but we don't
have the production. If the production is
achieved, we can reach some 300 factories
in the next 20 years, around, enough
factories, industrial zones. We can get
rid of a lot of things. We have done some
tests. 90% of the
oceans, what you call them,
we see them getting destroyed now. All
the lives - we see it by Australia. We see
it by most of the South Pacific and
South Atlantic. They're losing all the
prostrations, which is taken centuries and
thousands of years to build up. The
seashells they're dying because of the,
they say it's CO2. This... we have found the
reversal for it. When you look all the...
(CK) The corals, you mean? (MK) Coral reefs, coral reefs - partially yes. We
have found the solution for them, they don't
need to go gray. There is a
solution we can just add in the
environment of them and corals come back
to life. They just chang the condition.
We can change the same with the
plastics.
We have done a lot of research, there is a lot of
solutions. We have found a lot things can
be done. But, we don't have the production
and that's why we're involved in. I was
with some diplomats, they are trying to get them
to join the Keshe Foundation as a nation,
to to be part of this program this
afternoon. (CK) I have a very strange question
for you Mr. Keshe. (MK) Yes Mrs. Keshe. (CK) You know, for still a while people will
still be abusing plastic, and plastic will
be rolling off the production line. What
if we can add to our shops... I don't know if
it's possible, it's just something I just,Ncame to my mind. Can we sell
like production kit, that people can then
apply their plastic integration at home?
Like... (MK) You see we are finding a lot of use for plastic bottles
and plastic bags. It's amazing what we
are finding. If we use, when we use
plastic bottles in farming, we get a
beautiful result. This year we have nearly
100.000 square meter, actually
250,000 square meter, under cultivation,
and we are testing with plastic bottles.
And the farmers are going crazy with it. We
expect anything between three to six
times harvest. Because, once we create the
condition - a specific way of GaNSes in
the bottles, the CH bond of the bottle
itself, it becomes a source of fields.
Because, if you consider... you put GaNSes
in two bottles and just think they're okay
50 meters apart, 100 meters apart. or
whatever. Now in reality, the structure of
the bottles, this CH is in the gaseous
state partially, not in a matter state,
even you look at it that way. We are
doing a lot of work, a lot of Keshe
Foundations are doing work like this. And
we are looking at plastic pipes. A lot of
huge farms in farmlands use what is
called 'drip systems',
which is a plastic pipe - just drips
water on the roots, on the base of the
root of... doesn't matter what it is. And we
have found out we can use the plastic
effectively in farming. Very effectively in farming.
Is... we cannot get rid of it. They
can bring as much restriction as they like.
Packaging without plastic, at a moment, is
zero possibility. And one of the problems
they don't push with degradable plastic,
is very simple.
They say one year, two years. You buy
something and you forget it in the back of the
shelf. You come to it, it is all gone. The
security and responsibility of degradable
plastic a lot of people are
pushing, has implications. Huge
implications, because it has happened. They
create fire, they create all sorts of
problems. They increase the rat
population. People don't want to hear.
A lot of people are pushing for degradable
plastic. You buy a bottle of coca-cola,
degradable six months, twelve month,s one
year; and you happen to put it in a place
where there is an electric connection, and it
just starts degrading. A lot of
research is not coming to public and
public push for it. There is a problem.
Even though a lot of people say we don't
use plastics and everything else; and
this week, some nations as of today
actually, have banned certain kind of plastics. You
cannot do.
High density and low density bags are
part of our life. We have to have a
choice when we dispose of them, not when
they dispose of themselves. These are a lot of
current problems. There are two things
public have to learn - there is a public
LDPE service and public CAP service. We cannot....
degradable plastic has been ruled out
nearly five years, even though they said
they are working on it. The hazards, which
is creating is beyond imagination.
You can... Somebody's microphone is open.
There is a lot of problem with plastics.
You put medicine in it. What happened in
two years, three years just opens up,
degrades and you have a child passing and
taking it. The, we have to find an
alternative to dispose of it in a safe
way, which we have a... It is one of the
things is our priority in the new
factories and research centers. We see
how can be done - it's very easy to
degrade it. But then you have another
problem, is that you see so much plastic
on the oceans, we have the facilities we
have the knowledge to unwind them - we are
not destroying them. You can create a
condition that they just open up and
convert to hydrogen and carbon.
there'll be a huge depletion of what we
call
agriculture, because what we understand, if
the C and H become available in the presence
of water they extract nitrogen to
create protein. And there'll be certain
places where you create so much protein. And
then they set an amount the planet
produces protein through... in conjunction with
nitrogen. This is this has to be
controlled very, very drastically - quickly.
And it has to be understood. It has become
so entangled, people don't want to
understand this game of cleaning up.
Getting rid of plastic has become a
noose around the neck of man. You will have
a lot of oil, in the bottom of the ocean,
but you don't have enough protein or the
plants to feed. This  a lot of
things. Now the new science, the new
technologies, new data. There is
a hypocrisy, we say Amazon produces
1/3 of the Earth, or 1/5 of the Earth
oxygen. But what calculation has been
done, part of Amazon extracts
oxygen from the atmosphere, because it
has so much animals, that it just
produces enough to hold on its own
animals. They breathe it all in. The
data, scientific data nowadays is so
precise with satellites, that we see it.
Amazon, despite you know what they said
oil is from the fossil and from dinosaurs,
and we all accepted. Now, in the past 12
months, 18 months what we se in the pattern
of Amazons -
these are all huge forests areas we see -
they produce enough to sustain lives,
which are in it.
Amazon sometimes runs short. There are so much
animals living in it and breeding, that
they are consuming it. In a way, these trees
are developing more for the animals
inside them to be able to live. Is huge.
Now we understand totality. Now we
have extracted so much CH bond as
different form of plastics, that if we
get rid of them, most of us most probably
come up with diseases we have never known;
most of the plants will die around the
world. Because the release of so
much carbon and hydrogen in the seas,
where there's oxygen available and we have a
salt - leads to creation of protein. You
have plenty of fishes in the sea, or you
have plenty of oil at the bottom of
it. But we know there is a ratio that
Earth, in interaction with the Sun,
creates protein, or through existence of
nitrogen. And when we take the nitrogen
so concentrated in one place, this is
what is going to happen. I was explaining
this very recently in the
communication. You know, when they say when
people - the first ships - went to America.
Tens of kilometers before they get to
the shore, that couldn't go in. And
Christoph Columbus had problem getting to
shores, because there was so much fish - so
thick with fish. We're going to see that, most
probably, but in a different form.
There's... this dysplastic is not just
cleaning up. What are we gonna do? How
much are the damages we are going to
accept with it? We can't give fish to the
plants to eat. They need the nitrogen
protein level for themselves. Or we
deplete certain strength nitrogen that the
body of the man needs. What diseases will
come of it? It is so complicated. We
looked at this, we are looking at this
continuously. Corals we can change. We
can change very, very quickly.
We need just conditions that finally
changes the coral area into converting
the CO2, which in
conjunction with the water becomes the acid.
You can convert it very, very easily. As
part of the research now, we are opening
research centres in China and the
environment is one of the water and
decontamination of corals. We understand very,
very clearly. It will take us two or three
hundred years controlling to convert the
plastic.
They say if you further develop the way
they crush the plastic and they add it to the
tarmac. But how much streets left or roads
we can use them in? We have created a
mess. (CK) That, yes. But that's what my
question was. If we start,t like the way
we started the production of the CO2 kits. If we
can break down plastic as soon as they're
finished using it, and knowing the
conversion of it, then at least we have a
starting point. Not to top up what is our such a huge problem.
Do you understand. (MK) Yes I understand. But at the moment there is
a technology developed - we are aware of it\,Nwe've seen its operation - that converts
most of the plastic to energy, electric
energy. The recovery of the plastic from
rubbish and conversion, is nearly 90%,
95%. It is developed by the Chinese,
Chinese government. We looked at this
machine. And it is a conversion of all
the plastics to electric energy. That is the
closest, safest way we can do it. With no
emission, zero emission. I've seen the machine. I've been around it.
PART ABOUT ZERO EMISSION ENGINES COMPANIES ARE NOT INTERESTED IN....
and it's not gonna clean up anything,
it's gonna make it worse, but we got to
see. This plastic situation, if we...
We are not the only one. There is a lot of
technologies for it. You can use it, but
it's horrendous what's going to do to us.
It's a cat which is out of the bag, out of the womb of the Earth, and we
cannot get it back in, and we are still producing
more, and more of it. (CK) Mr. Keshe, with you referring
to the cat out of the bag, of the womb
of the Earth. You said in one of the
teachings, that it does matter if they
have depleted the layer of oil. You
said that the magnetical field strength is
still there in place. Is there any
possibility, with your knowledge, to
replenish that layer of what has been
distracted with the same? (MK) It gets done over time. You just have to find the next one,
while this is getting filled up. We were
discussing with senior people in the
government, very recently. They said, 'We
would like to clean up the under water.
There is a huge contamination of the
under water.'. I said, 'yes, but which part of
the technology do you want me to give
you?'.
But there is a problem. As long as you
don't clean up the surface, which feeds
the bottom, there is no use trying to get rid
of the poison in the bottom, because it
keeps on washing in. We got to change the
atmosphere, environment on the top, give
it 3 -10 years for it to wash
into the deep reservoirs. And then yes,
it's cleaned up. Primarily we can
apply a technology to do, but we don't
clean up the source. It's one of the
problems. We cannot take one piece
anymore and say we solve this one. We
have to look at it from the structure
A to Z. Then we can solve the problem.
There is a huge... the Earth will pull
in, it will create enough oil. Just
give it time.
Maybe... I reckon it takes about 18-20 years
to fill up the oil reserves, and they'll
never finish. So if you tap into it,
the more you pull, the more it gets
pulled, but in his time to convert. I was
with the oil men, from a Saudi oil,
and I was telling him, 'why are you building such a
huge refineries?'. 'Oh', he said. 'It creates so
much jobs.' I said, 'come with my
technology, I produce what you like, you do not
need the refining.
We got to teach slowly, but the
government's are not there to learn slowly.
We have huge transition time and the next
cycle, next maybe 200 years, our children
still clean up the mess we have
created. It's just like, we had a party
and leave all the dirty dishes and the thing
for mom to come and clean up. Or
someone's going to clean up. This generation
of us, those of us who were born in the fifties and
sixtie, have had such a big party, we'll
take our great-grandchildren maybe to
clean up the party we had. If you look at...
We are going into recycling, recycle
everything. But, if you know how much
glass we have produced. All these huge
buildings, all these sheets of glass, all
these glasses we have produced - something
like about 20% of it is getting recycled.
Nobody has looked at this glass
situation. All the steals, all the metals
we have produced, we used. Our
generation trying to develop our lives
to be modernized, have created a mess, that it will take
centuries to clean up. Centuries, if we ever
be able to clean up.
The fish, 300.000 pounds,
small fishing boats. That is 150.000 kilos
of fish in one trip - 3 to 5 days trip. And how long do you
think these seas are gonna answer, are gonna be there. And then it is sold at ten cents a
pound, 20 cents a kilo.
This planet soon is gonna cry. I don't have
enough to give - it's like a mother, which
goes you know, the brest goes dry and
cannot breast-feed the child anymore. We are
getting to it. We are pushing it to see
when he it is going to dry up. We are taking
every strands over strain out of it.
You understand, there is something very logical
behind the whole system. How much protein
can this farmer produce to sustain life? He can
sustain maybe 300-400
thousands of times, more than what he has now.
But then it comes different elements of
that, so we have to mutate.
This is part of the space technology we
are looking at with what we provide to
man,
how would he mutate in the space. He has
to mutate. We cannot create the
atmospheric condition of this planet all the
time. We can create fields to be
straight enough to what ????