with his soul. In so many ways, we got to
go back to the basic and make some small
corrections, or add to the knowledge to
be able to go to the next step. If we
look and understand how, in which steps,
mankind has taken a step and has gone
through the process of creation a lot of
mysteries about: the life of the man,
operation of the life of the man, the
soul of the man, operation of the soul of
the man, operation of physicality of the
man - all can be understood. All can be
taken to the next step. All can be added,
or can be understood to be added.
What does this mean? One of the
fundamental problems, in the whole cycle
of the understanding of the physiology
of man, is the construction of the
physicality of the man, and how
everything has been based on one, or two
elements, but man has calculated
everything else but these one or two
elements. This is very much, this is very
much like we have missed half of the
equation. We have missed half of the
knowledge. We have missed part of it,
which was really there and we didn't see.
Or, we never understood, that this is part
of totality, this is part of we have been
missing. This is in essence part, which
will bring us, forces us, we have no
choice but to understand it. To be able
to continue with it. To be able to
extract from it the real knowledge.
And in so many ways, this Carbon-14, as
an energy of the plasma, as energy of
the fields of the plasma, has never been
understood, in clarity. And man has made,
because of his presence, a lot of
mistakes in this structure of the
amino acid of the body of the man.
It causes cancers and it cures cancers .It
creates the destruction of the
connection layers of the brain of the
man. Leads to your age, your stroke. Leads
to understanding of the total work.
It affects every operation of the
physicality of the man. It affects every
operation of the soul of the man. It
affects every connection between the
soul of the man and the soul of
physicality. And most of the time the
world of science has never considered,
never understood, that... what this means. What
can be created, what can be given, what
can be added, what can be amalgamated
from understanding of the work of the
Carbon-14.
One of the problems of it, is that the
scientific world has not managed to
produce it - the way it works in the body
of the man, in the what we call as a
GaNS condition, as a plasmatic
condition. It has a sequence, it repeats
itself in different combinations, and because
of its dynamism, and it's what you call
separation of the physicality from the
neuro system, man have always ignored it.
If you look in the dimension of the work
of nitrogen, we look to the work of
Carbon-14, and we look into operation of,
like CH3, it has and should have given us
a lot of clues. We should have understood
a lot clues. I spent a lot of time today in
trying to explain the work of Carbon-14,
because it's something... it is so fundamental
that it needs a time to be spent on it,
because now you will understand the work
of the transmutation. How transmutation
becomes possible? It comes the work of
transportation across the universe. It
comes from the point of insulation and
isolation of the fields of the universe.
[Somebody's microphone is open.] It comes
to understanding the totality and the
relationship, between different part and
structure of the physicality, and the
soul of the man. And in so many ways, is
the pathway of the soul of the man, to
connect with the Universal Community, in
the path of the line of communication.
When we spoke about the carbon in CO2. When
we use it for conductivity and
connection in our medical applications,
or in other fields. Carbon-14 is the same
but in the dimension with a connection
with the soul of man, and physicality of
the man. Is the pathway, the way, the... as
call it, the wire, the string, where the
soul of the man leaves the physicality
of the man. Is the connection, where you
go - what you call a dream time - but it
knows where to connect to - happens
through that. It has a fingerprint of the
interaction of the soul. It has a
fingerprint of the interaction and action
of the universe. And in so many different
ways, we have to understand the work of
Carbon-14, carbon at all - all together.
What is a Carbon-14?! Rick can you pull up
on the Wikipedia, or a wiki, what is
Carbon-14 in a matter state? Can you get
it?
(RC) Yeah, yes sure, just a minute Mr.Keshe. (MK) What is
interesting, you got to understand, we
look at Carbon-14 in a plasmatic state,
not in a matter state. But in so many
ways, if we look at a Carbon-14, in
partially in the world of the science,
the present science, they call it graphene. It
behaves that way, in some occasions.
Because it looks as to be the end, and at
the same time, is the beginning of every
nerve. One end of the neural system, where
your nerves stop, is the orientation
of the Carbon-14, which creates the
feedback. It's Carbon-14, which gives you
the isolation at the point of amputation,
and the release of energy, as what we
call it - phantom pain. And it's part of
the whole structure of our existence in
real life. Would you like to read it for
us?
(RC) Ammm, sure. Okay, yyymmm, my microphone.... jest a second. (MK) Has the fire alarm gone off?
and you are back. Okay, I read it.
It says: "Carbon-14, radiocarbon is a
radioactive isotope of a carbon, with an
atomic nucleus containing six protons
and eight neutrons. Its presence in
organic materials in organic material is
the basis of the radiocarbon dating
method
pioneered by William Libby and colleagues
to date archaeological, geological and
hydrogeological.... something." Somebody is on
my screen, or is somebody... is it you
playing with the background? (RC) I was going
to make it larger if you want to leave it there, or
I could read it if you like. (MK) No, no it's okay,
carry on reading it, because we have to
understand this.
Carry on. (RC) You want me to read then,
is that what you are saying? (MK) Yeah, yeah. I read it. I read it
up to the first bracket, 1949, yep. (RC) Yep, so okay. So
"Carbon-14 was discovered on February
27th, 1940, by Martin Kamen and Sam Ruben
at the University of California
Radiation Laboratory in Berkeley,
California. Its existence had been
suggested by Franz Kurie in 1934. it
goes on to say, "There are three naturally
occurring isotopes of carbon on Earth:
carbon-12, which makes up 99% of all
carbon on Earth; carbon-1, which makes up
1%, and carbon-14, which occurs in trace
amounts, making up about 1 or 1.5
atoms per 10 to the twelfth atoms
of carbon in the atmosphere. Carbon-12
and carbon-13 are both stable, while
carbon-14 is unstable and has a
half-life of 5730 years plus or minus 40
years. Carbon-14 decays into nitrogen-14
through beta decay. A gram of carbon
containing one atom of carbon-14 per 10
to the twelfth atoms will emit about 0.2
beta particles per second. The primary
natural
source of carbon-14 on Earth is cosmic
ray action on nitrogen in the atmosphere,
and is therefore a cosmogenic nuclide.
However open-air nuclear testing between
1955-1980 contributed to this pool.
The different isotopes of carbon do not
differ appreciably in their chemical
properties. This resemblance is used in
chemical and biological research, in the
technique called carbon labeling:
carbon-14 atoms can be used to replace
nonradioactive carbon, in order to trace
chemical and biochemical reactions
involving carbon atoms from any given
organic compound." Do you want me to continue? (MK) Can you repeat that last
sentence? (RC) Okay. I'll say the whole paragraph,
it might make more sense. (MK) Ok.
(RC) "The different isotopes of carbon do not
differ appreciably in their chemical
properties. This resemblance is used in
chemical and biological research,
in a technique called carbon labeling:
carbon-14 atoms can be used to replace
nonradioactive carbon, in order to trace
chemical and biochemical reactions
involving carbon atoms from any given
organic compound. (MK) And, if you go back to
the first line, of the top paragraph. (RC) Ups, just a minute.
(MK) Just go up.
It says, "carbon-14 is a radioactive
isotope of carbon", and then it says at
the bottom: "Carbon-14 can be used to
replace nonradioactive carbon, in order
to trace chemical and biological reactions
involving carbon atom for any organic
compound." And when you read it, it says it
decays to nitrogen, but all this is in a
matter state. In the condition of the
plasma body of the man, and in the
dimension of the universe,
what does radioactive means? Means
energetic; and the energetic dimension of
this Carbon-14 is absolutely amazing,
because it's not being a beta decay, it's
being a dynamic, plasmatic fields, which is
continuously, travels beyond the speed of
light, on the matter state. The reason for
it, which has never (been) understood. Or now
maybe it can be explained? Is... neutrons are
the source of the energy, because they
want to decay to create stability. They
split into a proton and an electron
to create
stable condition for themselves. But, in
the case of the Carbon-14, you have two
neutrons, at the same time busy releasing,
and in that process to do dynamic point
centers, trying to balance, or create a
balance in their field interaction,
creates a line of insulation. A line of
magnetic field, which does not accept
anymore
because at the moment it has circled
itself. In the term of magnetic
insulation and isolation - when you have
the double neutron-base, like this. It
means that the matter state of it is
within itself.
It isolates itself. hIt has a huge amount
of energy to release. And that gives a
very high dynamic center to its carbon
structure - the other 6 protons and
neutrons, and it literally, it catapults
this material. A normal carbon does not
behave like this. A radioactive material,
which means has a huge amount of energy,
in a plasmatic condition has a huge, huge
amount of energy, which in balance with
having no electron to feed off, to
split into, that it can create a balance
of itself to become an atom. It creates,
what I call, super bullet out of carbon-14,
and that allows the man to travel the
depth of a space, as a few. If you can
replicate it. It teaches a lot to those of
us, who wants to understand. Because of
this
higher-speed, it creates a line of
transportation for the field matter
states of it. Carbon-14 is a plasmatic-
radioactive, not matter-state radioactive,
if we can call it that way. It's a source of
energy, which is so much, is like a virus
sit around the nucleus of the carbon. And
because of that amount of energy it gives
to it, it just makes a fire ball out of
the others. It is a free engine, it is a free
energy resource for the structure. And
when you enter in the dimension of
the matter state, a lot of doctors, a
lot of doctors make a mistake between it
and nitrogen. It's the cause of many
cancers, but it can be understood due to
its weight. Compared to the other carbon,
it leads to the combination of matter
state interactions. It's a massive ball
of fire, and this fire does not stop.
Because energy released by one Neutron
to go through, what we call splitting, what
to become nuclear decay is; automatically
absorbed by the other Neutron, and in
that process, in the dynamic magnetic
fields, part of the energy given to
other protons and neutrons - they become
active too. And in so many ways, if you
understand aging by, what we call, carbon-14
dating, should give you very clear
understanding - is the time when you stop
the whole process. Then you can trace it,
when and how it was stopped by itself, or
in the process it went through, a condition has
to stop, because of lack of transfer of
energy. Interesting enough, if we go to
the next step and understand that you
have a carbon and you have a, in a way
a Tritium. Two cells working together.
Two cells working, in a way, as a helium, or
in a way, as a Tritium, and sometimes due
to their energy balance, they behave as
just two neutrons.
What is, this will give, is the extension
in how to understand we age. How fast we
age and why will we use the GaNS plasma
technology on the cell of the man,
we see huge changes. Because we interfere
with line of field transfer energy. This
is why our CH3 GaNS shows a lot of
characteristics of Carbon-14. And if we
understand it we can fully utilize it.
[Air blowing]
When we take measurements on the decay
of whatever, we always make a mistake in
conversion of the energy of Carbon-14
with nitrogen. It's so common that because
of it we have missed many, many parts of
to whole structure of the understanding
of the work of the body of the man.
What I would like to do, I would like to
take you to a step to understand this
process.
I need a whiteboard. Rick would you like
to write in my place, because I cannot,
I lost my screen again. (RC) Ok, well we
do see your whiteboard right now but....
(MK) Yeah, but I don't have my screen pad. It's
okay, I write, no problem. When you have a
hydrogen, if your look, it's not an atom in
a way, it's a half atom, because it
doesn't carry any neutrons. It's the lack
of neutrons in it. The next step here is
nitrogen, or if we can put it, Carbon-14.
Very strange things, how I cannot use my
system. Then you understand the process
0 to 14. Now the next 14 comes here.
Again Carbon-14 but it shows itself as
silica. In that process of....
I've got a problem in writing this down. The next
14, Carbon-14 is silica. You understand, you
see it there, another 14. One of the main
components life of the man. When you take
this to another step - 28,
14;
and another 14, is dynamic, 42.
Can somebody tell us what's this 14?
In transition of the strength of the
magnetic field, is Mr COHN. Now I
appreciate what a beautiful thing I had,
as a pen. If you look at this, again...
What does it take us to? Where does it
take this to?
You come to something very easy. (AG) 56. (MK) Yes, I
know, I just don't have my screen. Hi Armen,
how are you darling? (AG) Good.
(MK) That's good. Now you see, how Carbon-14
has been the backbone, and different
combination of it - here is 56, the next
one is 70. And then look what 70 does,
which element sits with you at 70. But
you have to remember something very
strange. Here, we don't see usually as
such, what takes place has another
element we know, with number 42.
Then you understand how much our
scientists of the past have forgotten
and have not seen. Because they never
considered a dynamic structure that none
of it, one of it,
two of it, three of it,
four of it has created the cycle of life
on this planet for mankind.
And look at the half balance lines, and
then you see how life of the man has
gradually taken shape on this planet.
This raises a fantastic question, and
that is very, very simply; very, very
simple: Would the body of the man, would
the body of the man working on a Carbon-14,
will suit to travel the depth of the
Universe on the lines of the Carbon-14
magnetic field of the Universe? It is
absolutely a perfect match.
And if you look at this zone, you look at
this zone, and then you look at every
other zone with Carbon-12, then you
understand how the soul of the man and
the physicality of the man, physicality
of the man, the soul of the man
continuously repeat themselves. And
that's how we dream. And this is how the
two are so close to each other, that we
have lost sight of our soul, line of
communication of our soul. Where through
the physicality we communicate energy
transfer to come on top, but the work of
the Universe through transfer of the
soul is Carbon-14.
And we live through carbon-12, our soul
lives in the line of communication of
carbon-14, and this is how we will travel
the space of the universe. Then you
understand how easy should be for
mankind to become travelers of the
Universe. Every indication on the
transfer of gravitational-magnetic field
of the space of the speed of the
universe, sits within the structure of the
amino acid and physicality of the man, in
a dimension of magnetic fields. You're a
perfect match.
Now, does the man understand that much, that
in checking the physical dimensions in
matter state, sees silica, nitrogen, amino
acid and iron; or is it in reality
multiple combination of carbon-14?
Then it comes to us, a new dimension
in the line of communication for control
of the space reactors. Understanding the
creation of the soul and dimension of the
emotion of the man in the line of
physicality, and the soul of the man.
To understand how to travel, how to
nourish, how to multiply in the depth of
the Universe or anywhere in the Universe.
I warned the knowledge seekers yesterday in
the teaching, in the private teaching -
what was coming. Those of you, who work
on the dimension of any transfer,
transportation in the dimension of a
structural conductivity of the
physicality of the man, or the soul of
the man. Now you have found a very big answer.
if you look, when you look at the Alex
beatz Magrav systems. You use CO2 for
communication line for diabetic and
everything else. Now, you can add the
dimension of the transportation of the
soul to it. Now man has two choices: Do I
want to travel in the dimension of the
slow of a carbon? Or, do I want to travel in
the dimension of super-speed of the soul?
Can I use the plasmatic-magnetic field
of CH3, which I can produce so easy, to
become the giver of energy, as carbon-14?
Is there a shortcut to it, or does actually
sugar behave like carbon-14 in super conductivity
of the energy of one hydrogen atom? Is this is why the
body of the man evolves so fast on this
planet? Because of the presence of the basic
sugar, which gives you a carbon-14? Which
itself, already very active, has an
additional way to release the energy of,
to become energy source of energy. Or is
the additional electron, or additional
neutron, or additional proton -
depends how you define it - becomes a
point that, due to interaction of the
two neutrons in carbon-14, in a physical
collision with the additional proton, lead
to release of energy, that man
needs to create and dynamism in the amino
acid?
And become the source of energy. In a way,
we introduce a barrier. When the bullet
comes,
let's absorb the energy off - and that
energy, with that bullet, the bullet
release continuously, is by the double
protons or neutrons, as you have an
energy confirmation in the plasma
condition, which with the interaction of
the lighter one - two to one - that is two
protons confirming with the electron as
a neutron. In the CH3 with a third one, is
like putting a barrier or creating in a
plasmatic field force, very much like you
create a motion. This is your two
hydrogens
and this is your single hydrogen. And in
process, where you already have a
carbon here - you create a release of
energy to the amino acid which, is bounded
to it. And this amino acid becomes active,
it receives energy, itu can survive. So, if
we can increase the binding of CH3, or a
carbon-14 in the presence of the body of
the man, which creates a continuous
supply into the amino acid. Which means
the amino acid does not need continuously to
deplete and then replete it, gives a life
of centuries to man, because there is no damage.
There is no continuous depletion
refilling it. This is how you can extend life on
this planet.
Simple understanding of the transfer of
the fields of the Universe, can make a lot of difference for the man, if the man understands what's going on.
(RC) Excuse me Mr Keshe, could we get you to just move your microphone away from mouth. A tiny bit, not too much. (MK) Is this ok? (RC) Yes, sure.
(MK) So, now you understand how we can even extend the life of the man, through understanding the operation of carbon-14. And how we can use this operation of carbon-14 to
create the fast dynamic motion of the protein or the body of the man in the dimension of the soul of the transportation.
Now the science of physiology and the science of the soul of the man (...).
Now we can understand much more. Now we
can act upon it.
We can operate through it, we can extend
the life with it, and then we do not
depend on a cycle of the rotation of one
thing we called the day, the year, or
anything else, which mankind has chosen
to call this thing. Now, which side of the
story do you want me to sing for you?
Have the scientists been right to
measure the decay of life of anything on
a carbon-14, or did they miss the boat?
Or, can we use the operation of carbon-14 to
create a new dimension for life of the
man in the space? Remember last week, when
I spoke about the separation of the gaps
between the galaxies? I spoke about carbon-14.
I start putting things out for you to
see what you understand till the next
time, till the next teaching. Till the next
time, might be next time, or the time after,
or time after. But the teaching now
starts getting meaning. It starts having
understanding, because if you can create
a condition of transfer of the energy in
the level of carbon-14 we can tap into
the universal transportation line. You
can tap into the understanding, creating
life for the others who are the
passenger of this line, to manifest
themselves in the portal of life you
create. All you do, you create a new bus
stop.
Would anybody like to take of here, of the
thing? I have created a condition,
which I can create in that replication.
If you want to understand, maybe we can
explain, It's the super conductivity within
the conductivity of the plasma itself.
Now you can imagine what the scientists
were telling us. Super conductive
materials, not only now you have the
super conductive materials in the form
of the nano-layering, now you have super
conductive path, to transport that - now that we understand
the body of the man is made of
GaNSes.
Start adding up!
But, do you want to invite everyone in? Or,
do you want to have a specific length, or
specific people? You don't want to invite
the cousins but you would like the uncles
to come. And you don't know if the uncle
will be dressed in the suit, or they'll come
in pajamas.
How do you manifest that, only the uncle
turns up and no cousins, only the cousins
come, you don't want the uncles?
Go back to your teaching. Go back to
understanding . G back to understanding
of the interaction of the fields of the
gravitational field with inertia, which
leads to creation of manifestation of
the material or matter state - then you
understand.
Then you understand you can create the
condition of the confirmation of
existence by introduction of the third
strength in the carbon-14, and any
passenger of Universe, which matches into
that, will manifest in your portal.
It's very much, when you create a matter
state with the interaction of the fields of
your cores, it's you who by introduction
of the inertia, dictates what matter from
the energy of the atmosphere will
manifest itself. In the case of liquid
and iron we manifested, we produced blood -
horrible. In a case of interaction of the
fields, we created gold, zinc, magnesium
and the other one, which we've see the test results
as was done. Independently to confirm
what is in collected. Now understanding
the transfer and transportation and a
connection between the soul of the man,
which now becomes the language of the
Universal Community in understanding of
this transportation line. Now, you can
invite friends home, and then you dictate
what friends and whose friends. I don't
want this. I want to see what it gives me,
at such and such a strength in the
spectrum of the magnesium, with the carbon-14,
and see which creatures of God come up,
appear - like the way inertia lead to
creation and manifestation of the energy
of the Universe in the gold or copper,
now we have learned how to manifest our
guests. But, you can use the same process
to become part of, to join into the link
of the super-highway of the universe. Till
your cousin or your son on planet Zeus
has created a condition of the amino acid
strength of your carbon-14,
which leads you to land there with him.
Now you understand.
Because in that dimension, you travel
through the communication line of high-speed,
through, what we call, the soul speed of the man.
Because, it is still its combination of
amino acid but still is dynamic, that
it can link into. Now it's getting trickier,
isn't it?
Very, very tricky.
Those of you who understood, those of you
who maybe understand in the future,
I have already understood and you have
already entered to produce the portals.
But be careful when you do.
What did your mother say when you were
young and you went on the street?
"Do not speak with the strangers, and do
not every time go out, come back home
with a cat and a dog." How many of you had
that? "Mum, it's the last, last cat I ever
bring. I promise you that."
Now we open you the portals,
who's gonna turn up,
and how would you have made the
confirmation and process of the soul
level, which you have invited?
What does this mean to you, those of you
who were hoping that something might pop out
of the jackpot?
(RC) In the Q&A, Mr. Keshe, Dimitri mentiones,
asked the question: "So when we use
the flight system of the soul of the man,
we are using carbon-14 within ourselves?"
(MK) I don't know. What do you think?
(RC) Well, he also followed up two minutes
later with another question: "So, using
carbon-14 within ourselves, is a result
of conduct?" I think that's when you
mentioned super-conduct-ivity.
Is the use of carbon-14
a result of conduct, in a way?
It's kind of a play on words, but maybe
it's true. (MK) What a beautiful day.
We don't leave guess work, it's understanding
and understanding the knowledge,
comprehending the totality. This is what
it's about.
it's about the total existence.
(L) Oh mr. Kesh? (MK) Yes?
(L) There is fantastic question... (MK) Would you like to
introduce yourself, please? We know who you are. (L) This is Ling, from
China, from the beautiful country and a
lot of people love you here.
Yes, I think you bring us so fantastic
teaching today, but that's reminding me
of a video - what I watched before. It's about
meditation from Buddhism teaching, and
from there, I remember it shows like a
white connection line, when the soul come
out from the body and travel in the deep
space. And it's always connected with the
physical body, so when you talk about
carbon-14 I was thinking, maybe that is
carbon-14 field, inside the body and
that they find the match strength of the
Universe's carbon-14, and then the soul
just to travels outside of the body. Is
that true? (MK) Yyymmm, the color of the brain of the
man is a strange key to the color of the
soul.
The... when we look at the structure of the
brain, we see a very white color, cream-ish
white color, and different points of the
brain has slightly different
cream-ish white color, which is
combination of the magnesium and carbon
and zinc. Because, if you have made a
combination of the magnesium, zinc and
CO2 in GaNS, and you just change the
ratio slightly, you get a perfect,
perfect match of the structure of the
physicality of the brain of the man, in
this dimension.
Has any of you ever made
GaNS of silica?
(JB) We've made a lot in Arizona. (MK) What color
is it? (JB) Tan. (MK) Pardon? (JB) Bright tan. (MK) Like what?
(JB) Like a cream, cream color. (MK) Good morning. How
many of you have made zinc GaNS?
(JB) Again, we made a lot of zinc. (MK) White-ish snow?
(JB) White-ish snow. (MK) CO2 is white-ish
cream-ish, silica is white-ish cream--ish.
Mr COHN, protein - transparent. Zinc -
white-ish, cream-ish.
Isn't the brain of the man, which holds
the containment of the soul of the man,
perfect match for man to become man of a
space?
Is this, or can we consider, as many of
you made, I presume the calcium GaNS too -
what color is the calcium GaNS? (SK) White-ish, cream-ish.
(MK) Can I say good morning?
(SK) And calcium has also an isotope 42, which
is stable. (MK) Good morning. Have we found the
joint and balance connection, between both -
the containment and control of the
physicality of the man, the containment and
control of the soul of the man?
Has our soul been traveling on a
dimension of the physicality of the man,
and that's why we dream through our soul
and it gets registered in the dimension
of understanding and memory of the
physicality of the man? Is the matter
state of the physicality of the man, the
copper? And the coating of it, of the same
balance strength - the nano-coating,
which creates the super conductivity through
dimension of the soul of man?
Have we lived a double life in life of
physicality, superseded or super covered
by the dimension of the super
conductivity on the level of one matter
state, which is connected to the universal
dimension? Which is, our soul has
already been built, been developed, and
been from the beginning on the direction
and in the presence of the soul of
totality of the Universe? You know what a
nano material is? Does not matter what,
the space gap is the same.
14, 14, 14 - it does not matter what material you
are. I spaced myself because I have a
field, which can link up with you in
double and triple.
Now half of the mystery of the life of
the man, maybe is sorted. Maybe now you
can understand,
how man has lived a double life.
Something, a mystery here.
This, it sits 78.
(RC) So, are you speaking about selenium in
that case, mr. Keshe? With the 78, selenium
is 78.96, or
something as it's weight. And selenium
is, I know, one of the essential elements
for the body and is deficient in many
soils - like in my local area, where I
happen to live? (MK) In your (...).
(RC) Sorry, pardon me. (MK) Explain.
(RC) Well, I just know that there's a local
organic gardener and she's mentioned to
me that selenium is one of the essential
elements. We see, you know, iron of course
is one, and of course the carbon, oxygen,
hydrogen and nitrogen; and I believe the
silica, as well is one of the
essentials.
And the thing is that, I think due to
certain conditions, local conditions, many
soils can be depleted of selenium. So it
ends up if we don't get it from... (MK) Ok, we are looking
as 74, 78. (RC) 78, yeah. (MK) Yeah.
(SK) It's five, five and half
times 14. iIt's not a multiple of 14.
It's an oddity because it's a little
further from seventy. It's five and a
half times 14.
(RC) So, we should, you mean it should be 56
plus 14 to go to the next step? (MK) 70, yes.
But now, if you look at 78... (SK) 70 + ???
(MK) You see, if you have a 56 and you have
another 14, it gives you 70. But, if you go up,
do half of weight of the atomic mass of
oxygen.
Then
you get the combination, gravitational
field forces of this planet, which locks
into it. Or, the other way if you look at
it - if you add part of magnetic field effect
of four oxygen, it's the same combination,
you will end up somewhere around the copper
and zinc.
If you take the combination mass
elements of oxygen, which attracts
and locks the man into the physicality of
this Earth, that ties up the energy of
the soul of the man to the physicality
of this planet, which gravitational field,
magnetic field forces of the
gravitational field of this planet, we
always said is oxygen; you go four times
16, then you see how zinc has become
part of the structure of physicality of the
man. Then you see, through the carbon-14
how the soul of the physicality of the
man has got tangled into the
gravitational field of the body of the
man. And then, you can see how the soul of
the physicality and the soul of the man,
have got locked into each other.
You don't understand - let me explain. Here,
I have a next step, yeah? Sixty-eight.
Here, I have
(?) 64. (MK) Now, here I have the zinc,
connected to magnetic field,
gravitational field of the oxygen, which
ties up with a gravitational-magnetic field
element of non-ferro but in GaNS' state or
plasma state of 68 of the
oxygen. Now you see, if I add the 14 here
to it - how the whole structure locks into
each other. Here,
you bring the emotion - dimensional
of the control. Now you understand?
Here. (JB) I think you drew that number of 68
and I think it should be 64 up there, on top,
where you circled. Should be 64. (MK) Ohh, yes 64, sorry.
Now you understand how the physicality
of the man, the soul of the man, and the
connection between the soul and a
physicality conductivity, have locked
into each other. And why when you dream,
you remember in the physical dimension
and you remember what the momma said.
And only happens in the dimension of
the magnetic field of the soul and the
common denominator of the 14.
Now, maybe you understand why we remember
everything of our dreams. Because we
bring it in, and we lock it in, into the
physical dimension.
It is very, very easy to understand. Our
man has got himself into the whole cycle
of creation. The atmosphere of this
planet has just created the condition,
and the availability of the field
forces. That's what has happened.
Combination of the carbon-14 and a
carbon, in line of the connection with the
physicality and everything else, has
continuously has played back and forth.
If you add six,
or seven of the half of carbon, itself
six to fourteen, you get twenty. What is
twenty? If you add half of the weight of
nitrogen to the nitrogen mass, which is
seven, you get 21,22 -
sodium. And then you see how the
structure has picked up. How man
has got trapped into the physicality,
just by accidentally having creating a
condition. One, to the physical dimension
of this magnetic field of this planet,
irrespective of its matter state, through its
gaseous state, which is the oxygen. One,
through the dimension of the matter
state of this planet,
which is through its carbon. And then, one in
the dimension of the strength of the
work of the universe - communication or
transportation line, which is carbon-14.
Man has always worked in all the three
dimensions. Now you know why you remember
your dreams. Why the color of the
body, the soul of the man, contained with
the white shade of the brain of the man.
Everything else is matching up to fit in.
Everything else is there
sitting - connection of the physicality,
connection of the soul of the man, connection
with a matter state which is come, come...
in a way is a compromise between the two,
and a gravitational-magnetic field of
this planet.
Every half or a carbon addition to
carbon-14, gives you connection with
your physical dimension.
Then you understand how the both
magnetical, to do with the gravitational
field, to hold on to, in a dimension of
the existence of the field of the plasma
of the body, has led to creation of the
same connection with universal
communication line and magnetic field.
One works in the dimension of
physicality., one works in the dimension
of the soul of the man, and one works in
the dimension of the soul of the
physicality. But the dimension of the
soul of the man and the dimension of the
physicality of the man, sits in its
dimension of the soul of the physicality,
which is through the blood.
That's how the link has been locked in.
This is how the field moves from
physicality dimension -
the blood, the copper, the zinc.
Now we can see the structure. Now we can
see how we can travel in the dimension of
the physicality, or we can travel in the
dimension of the soul of the man. If you bring
the inertia condition of the
gravitational field of the gaseous, which
we are totally in the plasma condition,
which is oxygen - then we have the
manifestation of the containment of the
physicality of the soul of the man.
Which is the zinc, which is the amino
acid, which is silica, which is carbon-14,
and a carbon.
Now mankind should be very easy for it
to understand, why even you dream,
and you remember your dream. Where it's
actually its communication on the line
of your soul, and you call the dream.
Some of you have enough influence on the
transformation between the carbon and
carbon-14, that you can even call it the
wish, but in fact you have understood
how to tap in to the soul of the man. Now you
understand when we were explaining how
you can control the space reactors with
thoughts, with a wish - I want to go to the
left.
Good morning John!
(JB) I'm awake and paying attention.
(MK) What made you to make so much silica?
(JB) Because right now our bodies are made
carbon-based, and now I've heard a
lot of talk in teachings about going to
a crystalline based, which is silica. So,
now it starts to make sense, because I
can see where that silica is is, comes in
the equation. (MK) But you can see how
silica controls Mr. COHN?!
(JB) Now I do. (MK) Now, does it mean that in
your systems, you have to always consider
to be connected to the use of amino acid.
(JB) We've always, we've always had.... everything
that we do, we connect the amino acids. (MK) You should be able to think and
your system should fly.
(JB) We just have to tweak a couple little
things and we'll be right there.
(MK) A little tweaking to do?!
Now, hopefully we see, we understand.
Why we dream in this level, but we live
at this level.
Now, where do you think a line of
connection to the strength of the soul of the man sits?
I'm still waiting. (JB) Right now it's a zinc -
64, but it's along the pathway of
carbon-14. Is the pathway to the soul.
(AG) 9th.
(MK) I'm waiting Armen. (AG) 14 times 9. (MK) Why nine?
(AG) No, not 14 times 9. (MK) Yeah, why
nine times? (AG) It goes to iodine.
(MK) Do you remember iodine, somewhere else
we mentioned, years ago? (AG) Long time ago.
(MK) Those who work out iodine, do you remember where it
came to?
(AG) What was the question? I couldn't hear. (MK) I
said, do you remember what was number one
iodine came to be? I think somebody
worked out that should be the strength
of the soul of the man?! (MK) Yes, you told us.
(RC) Yes, I remember that being mentioned as
well.
(AG) Is it correct? (MK) Very much so.
But you understand the position of and a
connection of with physicality. (AG) Now we do.
(MK) Now a lot of mysteries comes together.
You have to understand this, if you're
going to play with portals. Are you moving
the soul?
Are you moving the physicality? Because,
if you take the element of iodine - 126 magnetic energy fields,
it's in fact, 11 times, 11.5 times, taking percentage
of field conductivity of the carbon,
is around the interaction of the field
forces of the matter state of the body
of the man - which is carbon-12.
This is where the soul of the man, connects
to the physicality of the man, in the dimension
of their strength. After two years, three years
we just come back, to the same point again, but
now we understand what we need.
So, when you make your portals, the random
calculation is: how many times the
strength of the gravitational and
magnetical fields of carbon-14, gives you
the speed of the travel, in the dimension
of the lines of the transportation of
the lines of the fields of the Universe by
order of the magnitude. The speed of light
does not come into it anymore.
It's like they say, you have a yacht with
an engine, which can do.... or a boat with an
engine which can do hundred km/h,
but they don't tell you, the river
you are on is already traveling at 400.
So, when it comes to measuring and
understanding the transportation through
the dimension of the portal, or
dimension of the soul of the man; in so many
ways the dimension, multiple of
carbon-14, fits directly to the soul of the man.
In a way, if you look at it, you travel nine
times by speed, to the direction of
position. And then you can tighten it, by
the order of magnitude. This is the... We
are not talking about the speed of light.
Speed of light does not exist, it's only in the matter state. And it does not go trough phase-change. I was explaining that it in the teaching yesterday.
Somebody said we go through another
dimension, and I explained that very, very
simply. I was explaining to a number of Iranian scientists this morning. When you travel
with the speed of sound and you break
the sound barrier, as you go through it.
The aircraft with a pilot, does it change
on the other side of the sound barrier?
Does it become a different aircraft, or
does it become different man? Sound barrier is
again, is a magnetic field compression -
even you call it the air compression. An air is
made of magnetic fields.
So, when the man goes through the speed
of light in the matter state, when he
does, would he come out to a new dimension?
Or as you pass, every time does the
pilot becomes a donkey, and the plane
becomes a monkey and everything else
changes, every time you pass through? So,
you come to understand - you have found a way,
a measuring method. A way to be able
roughly guess, what speed you're
going to go, where are you going to go, and where
have you set the dimension to the amino acid
strength of the soul of the man,
to land down where you want to be. You move the
man through the strength of his soul.
(RC) Hello Mr. Keshe?!
Oops, should be just another minute or two for Mr.
Keshe to come back. Bear with us please.
(MK) ... moved in the dimension of the
soul of the man and he moved on.
(AG) We couldn't hear anything before you
said. (MK) Those of you.... I didn't say anything, I
got dropped off. I'm just back. You have not
missed anything Armen'jan.
(AG) Okay. (MK) And I lost all my pictures, but it's
good. Now we understand the process, now
we start learning how to make the
framework.
You have to make a common denominator
framework, which allows and respects, not
only the soul of the physicality - if you want
to go in the dimension of physicality -
but respects the soul of the man too.
A strange thing is, not many creatures
have this combination to be able to
travel the span of Universe. Now you see
the advantage of being a human.
Very, very few races come to this
combination.
Now we start building a framework.
We start putting new rules, new dimensions....
which is actually.... CH3....
Then, then you understand, how close man is to
be able to become the passengers of the
Universe.
Any questions?
(RC) Ok, thank you Mr. Keshe, and once again I'll
remind the attendees, they can put their hand
up and we can recognize you to speak. And
panelists can do that as they see fit or put your hand up.
And, we have a.... one question particularly,
from Angelina, as you were in there. She says:
"It is interesting to think about the
ratio between those elements. Why did
you pick up these specific elements? Are
they the ones that (...) the whole human being? (MK) I
didn't pick up - the gravitational field
force of this planet has done for
billions of years. Because it has to work
in both dimensions. You know, it's very
easy. You have to understand, it's very
easy. Easier said and then in the past maybe
48 hours, I've repeated it two or three
times. You travel 24 hours a day, with the
speed of the planet, you...., of its own. You
travel with the speed of 10.000 to
be the passenger of this solar system.
You travel with a speed of 100.000
to be the passenger of the Galaxy.
And you travel with a speed of 1 billion
to be passenger of the Universe. And
every one of them, therefore has a field
force effect on the creation of the man.
This is how, at the speed you travel,
the collision you create to lead to the
creation of. If the speed of this planet
was not 1500 or 1600, let's say, km/h
to create it's 24 hours, and you would have
traveled at 2200 rpm,
otherwise we call it km/h, that your
day was, let's say, 16 or 15 hours or
whatever it could be. Then that speed
dictates a different fields creation, in
respect to the atmosphere of this solar
system. And if that creates that speed,
which means should be another field
forces exerted by the Sun on the Earth,
or the combination of mixture of the
Earth itself, or our annual rotation
becomes 200 days on the same orbit,
means we are playing fast.
It means, we create, we produce
interaction of different fields and the
structure will change on this planet. You
turn up a grinding stone, and you hold
your knife fixed to the position. Does
it create the same spark at 1600, than
2200? It's totally different.
So, the environment of this Universe, the
speed of rotation of it, the speed of
rotation of the Earth, the speed of
rotation of the solar system - now we
understand has an effect on the
creation of elements, in the different
position of this solar system, or this
Universe, or this galaxy .And that
combination has it's enforcement on the
others. This is... go back to the teaching
past years, I keep on referring to many
times, in teachings, that we are not only we
get the, what you call, the fields or
radiation from the interaction of the
field of the Earth and Sun. We get
radiations, we get fields from outside
the solar system, which its interaction
affects our life. Other things affect us,
and it comes into it, it dictates part of
our structure. So, we are not just
connected to 24 hours field strength
of this planet, because now the field of
the Sun counts too. So, we have a common
denominator at the end of it, which is
carbon-14, which is again affects our
condition to the speed of the travel
of the matter,
I'm sorry, field strength of the soul
of the man. We call it a soul, but it's
the packages of the energy, which has in line
accepted to be in conjunction with the
fields of this planet.
You got to understand. very simple, very
simple principle, and that is: if we have
no motors, that we don't have, we don't
see any motors rotating this planet. Then
we have no motors to rotate the galaxies
in the spans of the Universe - how
stronger the field strength of
carbon-14, or the winds of the Universe
has to be, that it can create such an
interaction, rotation with, and cause of
the galaxy to rotate? The speeds of the
fields of Universe are many multiple
larger, than one billion. How you get one
of these, what you call the windmills,
children windmills, and blow on it - it has
no motor. The speed you blow the air,
dictates how fast it goes. And, still
there is so much surplus energy, that the
speed of the blade cannot catch up with,
or is not enough. If the winds of the
Universe can create the galaxies to move
at 1 million km/h, how
stronger they are, that in slowing down
in the interaction matter states, they
create? This goes back to what I keep on
saying, that no man has ever managed to
measure the speed of magnetic fields.
Be it in the matter state, be it in the
speed of the universal magnetic
fields. Then you can travel the speed of
the universe, at any speed depending what
you lock in yourself to, for what reason.
Then it's not 9 times, is order of
magnitude 9 times the speed of universal
magnetic fields. Because that energy of
the extra Neutron, is dictated and
controlled by the universal field forces.
Has no friction. Is purely on a speed of
the center, the principle matter speeds
of itself.
It's not anymore the order of, what you
call it - multiplication, it is in order of
magnitude. Then you understand, man,
that a speed of the carbon-14, must be
dictated by a higher speed of order from
outside the Universe.
Which condition of it, part of it, is
connected to the speed of the travel of
the soul of the Creator?
Then, can we create a portal, that can
attract the travelers of different
universes?
Now I hope, I hope you understand.
(RC) Mr. Keshe, Doug had asked in the Q&A earlier:
"Is this pure spiritual/plasma science
extending into the matter state science,
to help us combine the two dimensions?"
(MK) Good morning.
(RC) And we have a question from Christian, in
the Q&A: "I am passing on the question by
Holger, who cannot
attend. Can you please give us practical
advice and training, on how to use
emotions for communication with our soul,
or Soul?" (MK) Find a common denominator,
between the strength of the soul, line of
communication and the strength of matter
line of communication. It's somewhere
around 160,
which is ten times the magnetic
gravitational field of the, what do you call it,
oxygen, gravitational field of oxygen. If
you multiply 12 by 14 gives you
something like 166. And then, you have
somewhere between that and then
somewhere with iodine - which is a soul
of the man with the dimension of
containment of the strength of it. Now
you know the strength of it,. To contain
it, you have to be higher. Dividing what is 126, you
have to give a stronger cage, that you
can contain it - which is 166. If it is lower, it
escapes. And, if you find a combination of
the elements of, in so many ways, the
totality of the structure, which is, in so
many ways.... very, very much the containment
of the amino acid of the man.
Then it gives you the dimension of the
existence, taking into consideration
possibilities of all the fields. Because,
if you multiply 42, 43 by four times,
it gives you how it comes to be part of
the structure of the creation of the
matter state of the brain of the man.
Now a lot of things fits, doesn't it?
Now maybe you understand why we even have
a calcium scull?!
This is how, you understand why we have,
they find carbon-14 even in our bones. It
comes from the universal field forces,
not from the body of the man. And it's got
such a lapse, such a strength, that it is
easy to travel. It's a foreigner, it's out
of this world,
but it's part of the common denominator,
and has dictated the structure of the
man.
It's dynamic, but has a, what we call, a
beta-effect - as we call it. So it means, it
interacts with the matter state.
So,
calcium can block it, can hold it, can
contain it.
When you look at the brain of the man
you understand about the soul of the man,
and the creation of the physicality of
it. It creates a field force pull, that it
becomes part of its cycle.
[Now I have to teach something very, very strange but it's beautiful if you understand it.]
Man will understand how he's come to be
created.Yellow or this way. Okay,
let's look at something. Sorry about
this, I don't have my pen. I said will
it next week, to be able to make it.
This is your one part of your brain, this
is one part of your brain. This is what
you have as a beautiful soul. Sorry,
it's too powerful. You got to understand,
this little chap is dynamic, and now you
understand the strength of it. But, it
creates a gravitational-magnetic field
forces, which is equal, the same as you
extracted CO2 from the environment, very
much... I cannot do it as a white color, I use
yellow color, it gives you, it pulls in
and it creates your skull - calcium - due to
it's forces. But as the calcium comes
and sits, and finds its position, like the
crust of the Earth. Now, very much like a
dynamic lava, it grinds on it, and it
continuously feed itself from it, that
it falls in and it creates the seed of
the physicality of the brain of the man. But it's
pull gets it, continuously extending on
it, but inside grinds it, to get the
strength that it needs for its existence.
We look at the physicality of the brain,
but how come it's got that shape? There is a
magnetic field flow wind - as you call it
here. And what strength it creates and
it has, dictates the shape of this
wind.
This is like, when we give a water to
somebody, and we tell them: this is a
water but it's GaNS,
it has, it's not normal water, it has a
field around it.
- Excuse me sir, this is GaNS too, hyh? And your
soul is contained within the structure
of the GaNS, it has a wind around it too.
So it grinds to it, it releases field
forces of it. Now you might understand a little bit more.
Don't forget - read book number one. At
what point, or read number, book number
three, or very well explained in number
four. That, how the surface of this planet,
or any planet has decided. So, a skull of
the man is the same. It's the interaction
gravitational-magnetic field of the soul
in a different strength of itself, gives
the dimension of the brain. With its
atmosphere, gives the skull of the man.
And where it's lost it, has found a loophole,
or leak on it - it becomes the spine of
the man. And then you get legs and arms. And
then you get what you have to deal with,
with the physical part of this planet.
And beautifully covers the soul of the
man in it, through the dimension of physicality,
but we call it a neurosystem.
We are reaching,gradually, the point of
departure. We're all on the same train,
and we are getting to the terminal. In
this city: the airports, the train station,
the bus station, the taxis - all go from
the same destination. You're in a hurry,
you have the money, you fly. You're in a
hurry but you have time, you get a train.
You're in a hurry but you don't have
that much, you get a bus. But you can go
on your own, you get a taxi. You want to
travel with the speed of the soul, you
want to travel with the speed of
Universe, you want to travel as a
sightseer: "I would like to be on the
spaceship" - now it's the choice of the man. And I
have taught you all of it now, maybe a
little bit is still left.
With the spaceship, with the reactors,
with the cores - we showed you, if you would
like to go with a donkey.
Get sightseer, you have all the time in
the world - you want to get up, you want to
go?! It's your choice! You want to go fast,
it's too far - you can take a jumbo-jet
and go through the dimension of the soul,
but you have to understand. I told you,
when I take man to a space, I take him
not as a subordinate, but total
knowledge. It's his choice. I'm not
interested in building factories and
companies and whatever. I'm interested to
take the man, but sometimes I have to
bribe this little chap with some sweetie
somewhere - just to get him to the line
that he can decide and it's there.
There is another flight system but I
introduce you to carbon-14 dimension.
There is a much, much faster way than
this
but in time, when man (is) educated, we teach more.
But this is good enough - you are traveling
millions of times by the order of
magnitude of the speed of light, the guy said
we cannot travel.
Now you understand how fast the
knowledge is getting transferred. Most of
it you do not understand, because the
comprehension of totality is not there.
But most of it, as I said, we teach not
through the voice but the soul of the man
for the others, and in the future man
will understand - if you don't forget it and
just make a pyramid, then you forgot how
it works, huh? It's no good having the most
advanced washing machine in the house,
when you lost the manual, you don't know how
to operate it, huh? Keep the manual, learn
the teachings and then you decide - you can wash
it with your hand,
or you can put in on a high-speed clean.
Just don't lose the manual, because
suddenly say: "Oh the guy said that, a
thousand years ago"; I hope it won't be that long for mankind, but I showed
you how you can extend your life, if you
want to have a thousand years, just to
mess around. And if you're like Armen,
you want it yesterday.